indian-magic.com 2016-11-05

# IndianMagic - Privacy Statement

We respect your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to IndianMagic will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to [let us know](mailto:webmaster@indian-magic.com). 

### **Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:**

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.  
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

### **Browser information collected on the website:**

IndianMagic analyzes website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on our website. Our website logs **are not personally identifiable** , and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site.

### **Use of cookies:**

We do not use cookies on this site. However since we use outside companies to display ads on our site, these ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

### **Privacy of our email lists:**

Currently we do not maintain any email lists.

### **External Links:**

This site contains links to other sites. **IndianMagic** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Advertisements at IndianMagic

IndianMagic works with third parties, that serve ads to this site. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies. Their individual privacy statement can be seen at their respective sites. IndianMagic has no control over data collected by these sites.
